Hi, I'm Maureen and I work as a Solutions Engineer at Alteryx.
嗨 我是莫琳 我是 Alteryx的解决方案工程师
I'll be your instructor in this course,
我是你的教练
where you'll learn how to build a really great dataset to fuel your analytics.
您将了解如何构建一个非常好的数据集 以推动您的分析工作
For years, I've been helping customers create analytic datasets for their analysis,
多年来 我一直在帮助客户创建分析数据集来进行分析
and what I've learned along the way is that you
我学到的是你
rarely get one dataset that's in perfect shape,
很少能得到一个形状完美的数据集
totally clean, and has no issues.
完全干净 没有问题
To be honest, a lot of time can be spent working
老实说 很多时间都可以花在工作上
to get a dataset just right before it's analyzed.
在分析之前获取数据集
But why spend the effort?
但为什么要花工夫呢 ?
Well, we've often heard the term garbage in, garbage out,
我们经常听到垃圾桶里的垃圾
and well, your analytics will only be as good as the data you feed it.
那么 您的分析只会与您提供的数据一样好
In this course, you'll learn techniques used to prepare datasets for analysis.
在本课程中 您将学习用于准备数据集进行分析的技巧
By the end of the course,
在课程结束前
you'll apply these techniques to produce a robust analytic dataset.
您将应用这些技术来生成健壮的分析数据集
These skills will be used throughout the rest of the course and are
这些技能将在整个课程的整个过程中使用 并且
key skills used by business analysts in their jobs every day.
业务分析员每天在工作中使用的关键技能